Mattias Ewers



Email: mattias.ewers@gmail.com

Summary



Self tought Web Developer since 3 years currently working with React.js and React Native in ES6 to make apps. I have experience IT-Support but web development is where my heart is.

Skills



- Motion Graphics
- Graphics
- Social Media
- Programming
- CSS3

- Web Design
- Film
- SEO
- HTML5
- JavaScript Libraries

Experience

mattiasewers.com

07 / 2013 - Present

Front-End Developer

I work as a Freelance Web Developer if you want me to help you build your own website I would be glad to help!

Erik Olsson Fastighetsförmedling

03 / 2015 - 09 / 2015

IT Technician

Managing computers, cell phones and our internal systems. Helping all personnel with their problems.

Smyckendahls

09 / 2014 - 04 / 2015

Webmaster

Assignments including, SEO project manager, Photoshop, making newsletters, updating the website.

Sigtuna kommun

11 / 2013 - 03 / 2015

Personal Assistant

Education
Nackademin
Front-end Utvecklare
NTI Gymnasiet
2015 - 2017
2011 - 2014
Technologi, Film, Design, Webdesign, Graphics, Movies, Motion graphics, Video effects
• Svenska
• Engelska